<!DOCTYPE html>
<html lang="en-US">
<head>
<meta charset="UTF-8">
<title>Privacy Policy</title>
<meta name="title" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="DC.title" lang="en" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="description" content="Get expert tax preparation and filing services from experienced professionals in San Antonio, TX . We maximize deductions for individuals and businesses.Our San Antonio tax experts provide IRS and state tax resolution services. We assist with liens, levies, wage garnishment and all tax issues.Need help catching up on unfiled tax returns in San Antonio, TX ? We safely file past due taxes and help non-filers get compliant. Does your San Antonio business need tax preparation and filing? Our CPAs specialize in s-corps, LLCs, partnerships and small biz taxes.Get representation from our licensed tax audit pros in San Antonio, TX  if you're audited by the IRS. We negotiate favorable outcomes.Let our tax consultants help your San Antonio cannabis business with compliant tax filing and guidance through IRS challenges.We handle cryptocurrency, FBAR, FATCA reporting and other complex tax situations for individuals and businesses in San Antonio.Our San Antonio tax experts provide tailored strategies, filing and relief services for medical professionals facing unique tax issues.  Got tax return errors or need amendments? Our San Antonio tax specialists correct mistakes, get ITINs, and resolve filing issues.Looking to minimize your tax burden in San Antonio, TX ? Our CPAs know every deduction and credit to leverage maximum tax savings.File your taxes smoothly in San Antonio, TX . We make tax prep easy - just hand us your documents and we'll handle the rest!Our San Antonio tax attorneys assist at all stages of IRS disputes, from tax debt relief to audit defense and tax court representation.Received an IRS notice? Get expert tax relief help from our San Antonio team. We know how to resolve state and IRS tax issues.Our tax CPAs cater to small business owners and self-employed filers in San Antonio, TX . We maximize your deductions.Need tax debt relief in San Antonio, TX ? Settle back taxes, remove liens and levies, and rehabilitate your tax situation.Get specialized tax preparation services for remote employees, travelers, military and others with non-traditional filings in San Antonio.New San Antonio home owners - our tax pros can help maximize returns using home buyer deductions for mortgage interest, taxes, etc.  Our tax relief team assists San Antonio residents and businesses with wage and bank account levies, garnishment release, and more.We negotiate with tax agencies to remove IRS liens against your San Antonio home or business and resolve back tax issues.Filing business taxes for your San Antonio company? We handle sales, employment, licensing and local taxes with ease.Accurately report cryptocurrency transactions in San Antonio, TX  with help from our CPAs experienced in bitcoin, NFT and coin taxes.Get foreign tax guidance from our San Antonio CPAs on issues like expat taxes, FBAR/FATCA reporting, foreign investment taxes and more. Maximize Social Security benefits while minimizing taxes in San Antonio, TX . Our experts recommend tax-savvy retirement strategies.  Looking for tax-compliant accounting help with payroll, bookkeeping, invoicing or collections? Our San Antonio CPAs can assist. Our San Antonio tax professionals fight to remove excessive penalties and negotiate settlements for taxpayers facing IRS fines.Fast track your tax refund by ensuring proper filing through our San Antonio preparers. We know the latest IRS rules.Can't pay back taxes all at once? We assist San Antonio taxpayers in negotiating IRS payment plans and long term solutions.Our San Antonio tax experts help maximize returns for relocated employees, with deductions for moving expenses and job hunting costs.Get rapid tax dispute resolution from our San Antonio professionals. We alleviate the stress of owing back taxes.Let our tax office handle your San Antonio return smoothly from start to finish. Drop off your documents and we'll take it from there!Settle tax debts in San Antonio for less than you owe through IRS Offer in Compromise or other tax relief programs we can facilitate.Get our San Antonio CPAs' guidance on capital gains, property, and investment taxes to minimize what you owe on sold assets.Don't face confusing IRS letters alone - our San Antonio tax pros can explain notices and handle response correspondence for you.Our tax professionals serve San Antonio, TX  with IRS audit defense, tax debt relief, and preparation services for any situation, year-round.Sell cannabis? Work with CPAs familiar with Section 280E and cannabis business taxes in San Antonio, TX  for smoother IRS dealings.Paying too much in IRS penalties and interest? Get relief and a fresh start through help from our tax experts in San Antonio, TX .Affordable tax preparation and filing services in San Antonio, TX . Our tax pros help you maximize returns and get your taxes done right. Need tax relief? Our San Antonio tax experts resolve IRS and state tax issues. Help with liens, levies, wage garnishment & more!Get expert tax preparation for individuals and businesses in San Antonio, TX . We find every deduction to reduce your tax burden. File past due tax returns safely with our tax pros in San Antonio, TX . We help non-filers catch up on unfiled taxes.Got audited by the IRS? Get help from our licensed tax audit pros in San Antonio. We fight for the best settlement. Our tax consultants assist San Antonio cannabis businesses with compliant tax filing and IRS challenges unique to the industry. We handle cryptocurrency taxes, FBAR, FATCA reporting, and other complex tax situations for San Antonio clients.Need tax relief as a medical professional? Our San Antonio tax experts understand your unique tax challenges and can help.File amended returns, get ITINs, and correct any tax return issues with help from our San Antonio tax correction specialists. We know every deductible expense to minimize your taxes in San Antonio, TX . Our CPAs leverage tax savings for your return.Get tax preparation for your San Antonio small business from CPAs specialized in s-corps, LLCs, partnerships, and more.Our tax professionals in San Antonio, TX  make filing taxes easy. Bring us your paperwork and we'll handle the rest!We negotiate tax settlements through IRS appeals, offer in compromise and more. Our tax attorneys fight for San Antonio taxpayers.Got an IRS notice? Get legal tax relief help from our San Antonio experts. We know how to address any IRS or state tax issue. Self-employed or own a small business in San Antonio, TX ? Our tax experts understand your tax deductions to reduce tax burden. Resolve any back tax issues and settle IRS tax debt with help from our experienced San Antonio tax relief team. Need San Antonio tax preparation as a remote, traveling or military worker? We're experts on deductions for mobile lifestyles.Our tax consultants assist and represent San Antonio residents and businesses at all stages of an IRS audit or tax dispute.From W2 employees to military families, we provide thorough tax preparation services across San Antonio, filing taxes quickly.Want to lower taxes on social security income? Our savvy San Antonio tax prep team helps you maximize benefits and savings. New San Antonio, TX  home owner? Let our tax pros maximize returns through mortgage interest, property tax and other home buyer deductions.Got tax levy, wage garnishment or IRS collections impacting you? Our San Antonio tax relief team can help release them. Our San Antonio tax consultants fight to remove IRS tax liens from your home/business and resolve the underlying issues.We handle business license tax filing, sales tax, payroll taxes and all compliance needs for San Antonio companies. File accurate cryptocurrency taxes in San Antonio, TX  with guidance from our CPAs experienced in bitcoin, NFTs and digital coins.Get help from our San Antonio enrolled agents, CPAs and tax attorneys on any complex US expat or foreign tax issue.Our tax professionals in San Antonio recommend tax strategies to save for retirement and reduce taxes on Social Security benefits. Does your San Antonio small business need help with bookkeeping or payroll? Our CPAs offer tax-compliant accounting services.Get IRS penalty relief with help from our tax experts in San Antonio, TX . We fight to remove unfair penalties.Expecting a tax refund? Our San Antonio tax pros ensure proper filing to expedite IRS refund processing.We negotiate affordable IRS payment plans and options for San Antonio individuals and businesses needing to pay back taxes over time. Moved for a new job in San Antonio, TX? Maximize relocation and moving expense deductions with help from our tax experts.">
<meta name="robots" content="index, follow">
<meta name="googlebot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<meta name="bingbot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<link rel="canonical" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/privacy-policy.html">
<link rel="shortcut icon"  href="img/insognalogosite2020.png"/>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/css/bootstrap.min.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Kumbh+Sans:100,200,300,400,500,600,700,800,900&amp;display=swap" as="style" onload="this.onload=null;this.rel='stylesheet'">
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/jquery@3.5.1/dist/jquery.slim.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/popper.js@1.16.1/dist/umd/popper.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/js/bootstrap.bundle.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/font-awesome/4.7.0/css/font-awesome.min.css">
<style type="text/css">
.w6b89800bb312998a11906447a961b63a{
background-color:#ffc107!important;
border-color:#ffc107!important;
color:#000000!important;
}
ul{
list-style: circle;
}
footer{
background:#0b0b0b;
color:#ffffff;
}
.xa2c0134af9a229a000e41a246db9d20a p,.xa2c0134af9a229a000e41a246db9d20a span,.xa2c0134af9a229a000e41a246db9d20a label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
footer *{
font-size:16px !important;
}
.navbar a{
font-size: 17.7px!important;
font-weight: bold;
}
html{
scroll-behavior: smooth;
}
.btn-md{
padding: 15.1px 30.1px;
border-radius: 0;
}
a{
text-decoration: none!important;
}
.nav-link{
color: #000000!important;

}
footer a{
color:#ffffff;
text-decoration: underline;
}
*{
font-family: 'Kumbh Sans', sans-serif;
}
.x968e6817eebdfffc0a5d2d309558c651 p,.x968e6817eebdfffc0a5d2d309558c651 a,.x968e6817eebdfffc0a5d2d309558c651 span,.x968e6817eebdfffc0a5d2d309558c651 label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
.nav-item{
padding-left:8px;
padding-right:8.4px;
padding-top:5.5px;
padding-bottom:5.4px;
}
.y20633a2d6a8ea7b583980514c8da0f27:hover{
box-shadow: 0 49.5px 50.4px -25px rgb(0 0 0 / 30%);
transform: rotate(-2deg) scale(1.03);
}
.x968e6817eebdfffc0a5d2d309558c651 a,.xa2c0134af9a229a000e41a246db9d20a a{
color:#050505!important;
text-decoration: underline !important;
}
.xa2c0134af9a229a000e41a246db9d20a a{
font-size:16px;
}
</style>
</head>
<body>
<nav class="navbar-expand-lg navbar">
<a class="navbar-brand" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/index.html"  ><img alt="img/insognalogosite2020.png" src="img/insognalogosite2020.png"  width="150px" ></a>
<button class="navbar-toggler" type="button" data-toggle="collapse" data-target="#navbarSupportedContent" aria-controls="navbarSupportedContent" aria-expanded="false" aria-label="Toggle navigation">
<span class="navbar-toggler-icon"></span></button><div class="navbar-collapse collapse" id="navbarSupportedContent">
<ul class="navbar-nav d-flex ml-auto align-items-center"><li class="nav-item">
<a class="bf515758d605b587210d7f4efe1d63f6a nav-link" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/index.html" >Tax preparation service in San Antonio, TX</a>
</li>
<li class="nav-item">
<a class="nav-link bf515758d605b587210d7f4efe1d63f6a" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/tax-preparation-in-san-antonio.html" >Tax preparation in San Antonio</a>
</li>
<li class="nav-item">
<a class="bf515758d605b587210d7f4efe1d63f6a nav-link" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/tax-preparation.html" >Tax preparation</a>
</li>
<li class="nav-item">
<a class="bf515758d605b587210d7f4efe1d63f6a nav-link" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/cpa-firm-that-provides-tax-preparation.html" >CPA firm that provides tax preparation</a>
</li>
<li class="dropdown nav-item">
<a class="dropdown-toggle nav-link bf515758d605b587210d7f4efe1d63f6a" href="#" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">More</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu-right dropdown-menu" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/tax-preparation-for-small-business.html"  >Tax preparation for small business</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/s-corp-tax-preparation-in-texas.html"  >S Corp tax preparation in Texas</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/irs-payment-plan-help-in-san-antonio-texas.html"  >IRS Payment Plan Help in San Antonio, Texas</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/resolve-back-taxes-in-san-antonio-texas.html"  >Resolve Back Taxes in San Antonio, Texas</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/tax-lien-removal-services-in-san-antonio.html"  >Tax Lien Removal Services in San Antonio</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/san-antonio-tax-relief-for-small-businesses.html"  >San Antonio Tax Relief for Small Businesses</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/we-handle-irs-appeals-in-san-antonio-texas.html"  >We Handle IRS Appeals in San Antonio, Texas</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/non-filers-catch-up-on-unfiled-returns-in-san-antonio.html"  >Non-filers? Catch Up On Unfiled Returns in San Antonio</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/got-cryptocurrency-tax-help-in-san-antonio-texas.html"  >Got Cryptocurrency? Tax Help in San Antonio, Texas</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/navigate-tax-debt-for-medical-professionals-in-san-antonio.html"  >Navigate Tax Debt for Medical Professionals in San Antonio</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/self-employed-our-san-antonio-tax-experts-can-help.html"  >Self-employed? Our San Antonio Tax Experts Can Help</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/city-tax-guidance-for-san-antonio-businesses.html"  >City Tax Guidance for San Antonio Businesses</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/resolve-complex-tax-issues-with-our-san-antonio-cpas.html"  >Resolve Complex Tax Issues With Our San Antonio CPAs</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/tax-return-amendments-and-corrections-in-san-antonio.html"  >Tax Return Amendments and Corrections in San Antonio</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/irs-audit-representation-by-san-antonio-tax-attorneys.html"  >IRS Audit Representation By San Antonio Tax Attorneys</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/avoid-penalties-and-interest-with-tax-help-in-san-antonio.html"  >Avoid Penalties and Interest with Tax Help in San Antonio</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/tax-relief-for-cannabis-businesses-in-san-antonio-texas.html"  >Tax Relief for Cannabis Businesses in San Antonio, Texas</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/get-an-itin-number-with-help-from-san-antonio-tax-pros.html"  >Get an ITIN Number With Help From San Antonio Tax Pros</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/file-past-returns-to-obtain-stimulus-payments-in-san-antonio.html"  >File Past Returns to Obtain Stimulus Payments in San Antonio</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/we-handle-fbar-and-fatca-reporting-in-san-antonio-texas.html"  >We Handle FBAR And FATCA Reporting in San Antonio, Texas</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/cryptocurrency-tax-experts-serving-san-antonio-texas.html"  >Cryptocurrency Tax Experts Serving San Antonio, Texas</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/need-a-power-of-attorney-tax-help-in-san-antonio-can-assist.html"  >Need a Power of Attorney? Tax Help in San Antonio Can Assist</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/professional-tax-preparation-in-san-antonio-texas.html"  >Professional Tax Preparation in San Antonio, Texas</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/san-antonio-tax-service-file-your-taxes-here.html"  >San Antonio Tax Service - File Your Taxes Here</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/the-best-tax-preparers-in-san-antonio-texas.html"  >The Best Tax Preparers in San Antonio, Texas</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/san-antonio-tax-experts-accounting-tax-services.html"  >San Antonio Tax Experts - Accounting & Tax Services</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/trusted-tax-preparation-in-san-antonio-texas.html"  >Trusted Tax Preparation in San Antonio, Texas</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/file-your-taxes-with-confidence-san-antonio-tax-experts.html"  >File Your Taxes with Confidence - San Antonio Tax Experts</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/local-tax-preparers-san-antonio-tax-services-near-me.html"  >Local Tax Preparers San Antonio - Tax Services Near Me</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/san-antonio-tax-accountants-irs-audit-help-available.html"  >San Antonio Tax Accountants - IRS Audit Help Available</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/tax-return-preparation-you-can-trust-in-san-antonio.html"  >Tax Return Preparation You Can Trust in San Antonio</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/dedicated-tax-experts-serving-san-antonio-texas.html"  >Dedicated Tax Experts Serving San Antonio, Texas</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/convenient-tax-preparation-office-in-san-antonio-texas.html"  >Convenient Tax Preparation Office in San Antonio, Texas</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/let-our-tax-professionals-file-your-san-antonio-return.html"  >Let Our Tax Professionals File Your San Antonio Return</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/san-antonio-tax-service-missing-refund-we-can-help.html"  >San Antonio Tax Service - Missing Refund? We Can Help</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/file-past-due-tax-returns-with-our-san-antonio-experts.html"  >File Past Due Tax Returns with Our San Antonio Experts</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/amended-tax-returns-san-antonio-tax-professionals.html"  >Amended Tax Returns - San Antonio Tax Professionals</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/irs-tax-relief-assistance-in-san-antonio-texas.html"  >IRS Tax Relief Assistance in San Antonio, Texas</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/tax-audit-help-san-antonio-legal-tax-experts.html"  >Tax Audit Help San Antonio - Legal Tax Experts</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/san-antonio-irs-tax-debt-specialists-remove-liens.html"  >San Antonio IRS Tax Debt Specialists - Remove Liens</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/need-to-file-back-taxes-san-antonio-tax-experts-can-help.html"  >Need to File Back Taxes? San Antonio Tax Experts Can Help</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/owe-the-irs-tax-relief-services-in-san-antonio-texas.html"  >Owe the IRS? Tax Relief Services in San Antonio, Texas</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/san-antonio-tax-experts-payroll-bookkeeping-services.html"  >San Antonio Tax Experts - Payroll & Bookkeeping Services</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/tax-preparation-for-san-antonio-individuals-and-businesses.html"  >Tax Preparation for San Antonio Individuals and Businesses</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/san-antonio-tax-experts-for-complex-corporate-tax-returns.html"  >San Antonio Tax Experts for Complex Corporate Tax Returns</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/let-our-tax-cpas-lower-your-san-antonio-tax-burden.html"  >Let Our Tax CPAs Lower Your San Antonio Tax Burden</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/tax-minimization-strategies-san-antonio-tax-experts.html"  >Tax Minimization Strategies - San Antonio Tax Experts</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/san-antonio-tax-consultants-for-small-business-owners.html"  >San Antonio Tax Consultants for Small Business Owners</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/tax-prep-services-for-llcs-partnerships-in-san-antonio-texas.html"  >Tax Prep Services for LLCs & Partnerships in San Antonio, Texas</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/san-antonio-tax-accountants-estatetrustgift-returns.html"  >San Antonio Tax Accountants - Estate/Trust/Gift Returns</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/retirement-tax-strategies-san-antonio-tax-experts.html"  >Retirement Tax Strategies - San Antonio Tax Experts</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/reduce-taxes-on-social-security-san-antonio-tax-pros.html"  >Reduce Taxes on Social Security - San Antonio Tax Pros</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/tax-preparation-for-military-families-in-san-antonio-texas.html"  >Tax Preparation for Military Families in San Antonio, Texas</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/san-antonio-tax-service-moving-expenses-deductions.html"  >San Antonio Tax Service - Moving Expenses Deductions</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/job-relocation-tax-help-san-antonio-tax-consultants.html"  >Job Relocation Tax Help - San Antonio Tax Consultants</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/medical-expense-deductions-san-antonio-tax-experts.html"  >Medical Expense Deductions - San Antonio Tax Experts</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/education-credit-tax-savings-san-antonio-tax-preparers.html"  >Education Credit Tax Savings - San Antonio Tax Preparers</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/child-care-tax-credit-help-in-san-antonio-texas.html"  >Child Care Tax Credit Help in San Antonio, Texas</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/tax-deduction-for-new-home-buyers-san-antonio-texas.html"  >Tax Deduction for New Home Buyers - San Antonio, Texas</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/san-antonio-tax-service-file-home-office-deductions.html"  >San Antonio Tax Service - File Home Office Deductions</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/file-your-taxes-online-with-san-antonio-tax-experts.html"  >File Your Taxes Online with San Antonio Tax Experts</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/convenient-drop-off-tax-service-in-san-antonio-texas.html"  >Convenient Drop-off Tax Service in San Antonio, Texas</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/let-our-tax-office-file-your-san-antonio-tax-return.html"  >Let Our Tax Office File Your San Antonio Tax Return</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/local-tax-accountants-san-antonio-year-round-service.html"  >Local Tax Accountants San Antonio - Year Round Service</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/file-an-extension-with-our-san-antonio-tax-experts.html"  >File an Extension With Our San Antonio Tax Experts</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/got-an-irs-notice-tax-relief-lawyers-in-san-antonio-texas.html"  >Got an IRS Notice? Tax Relief Lawyers in San Antonio, Texas</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/avoid-irs-collections-with-a-san-antonio-tax-attorney.html"  >Avoid IRS Collections with a San Antonio Tax Attorney</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/settle-your-tax-debt-offer-in-compromise-help-san-antonio.html"  >Settle Your Tax Debt - Offer in Compromise Help San Antonio</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/get-penalty-relief-from-our-san-antonio-irs-tax-experts.html"  >Get Penalty Relief from Our San Antonio IRS Tax Experts</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/tax-levy-release-help-in-san-antonio-texas.html"  >Tax Levy Release Help in San Antonio, Texas</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/how-to-stop-wage-garnishments-san-antonio-tax-pros.html"  >How to Stop Wage Garnishments - San Antonio Tax Pros</a></div>
</li>
<li class="nav-item"><a class="nav-link bf515758d605b587210d7f4efe1d63f6a" rel=nofollow href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/about-us.html">About Us</a>
</li></ul>
</div>
</nav>
<section class="container" style="min-height: 80vh;">
<h1>Privacy Policy for Insogna CPA</h1>
<p>At Insogna CPA one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors.
 This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Insogna CPA and how we use it. You can check out our main website here: </p>
<p>If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.</p>
<p>This Privacy Policy only applies to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Insogna CPA. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website. </p>
<h2>Consent</h2>
<p>By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.</p>
<h2>Information we collect</h2>
<p>The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.</p>
<p>If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.</p>
<p>When you register for an Account, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name, Insogna CPA, address, email address, and telephone number.</p>
<h2>How we use your information</h2>
<p>We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:</p>
<ul>
<li>Provide, operate, and maintain our website</li>
<li>Improve, personalize, and expand our website</li>
<li>Understand and analyze how you use our website</li>
<li>Develop new products, services, features, and functionality</li>
<li>Communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the website, and for marketing and promotional purposes</li>
<li>Send you emails</li>
<li>Find and prevent fraud</li>
</ul>
<h2>Log Files</h2>
<p>Insogna CPA follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.</p>
<h2>Advertising Partners Privacy Policies</h2>
<P>You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of Insogna CPA.</p>
<p>Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Insogna CPA, which are sent directly to users' browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.</p>
<p>Note that Insogna CPA has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.</p>
<h2>Third Party Privacy Policies</h2>
<p>Insogna CPA's Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. </p>
<p>You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers' respective websites.</p>
<h2>CCPA Privacy Rights (Do Not Sell My Personal Information)</h2>
<p>Under the CCPA, among other rights, California consumers have the right to:</p>
<p>Request that a business that collects a consumer's personal data disclose the categories and specific pieces of personal data that a business has collected about consumers.</p>
<p>Request that a business delete any personal data about the consumer that a business has collected.</p>
<p>Request that a business that sells a consumer's personal data, not sell the consumer's personal data.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>GDPR Data Protection Rights</h2>
<p>We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:</p>
<p>The right to access – You have the right to request copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.</p>
<p>The right to rectification – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request that we complete the information you believe is incomplete.</p>
<p>The right to erasure – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to data portability – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>Children's Information</h2>
<p>Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.</p>
<p>Insogna CPA does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.</p>
<h2>Publisher</h2>
<p>
This website is owned and published by:
Insogna CPA</br>
512-891-8200</br>
700 N St Mary's St #1400</br>
San Antonio</br>
Texas</br>
</br>
</br>
</p>
</section>
<footer>
<div class="container pt-5 py-4" >
<div class="row"><div class="col-lg-3">
<p>Insogna CPA</p>
<p>Phone : 512-891-8200</p>
<p>City : San Antonio</p>
<p>State : Texas</p>
<p>Zip : 78205</p>
<p>Address : 700 N St Mary's St #1400</p>
</div><div class="col-lg-3"><p><a class="bf515758d605b587210d7f4efe1d63f6a" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/sitemap.html" rel="nofollow">Sitemap</a></p>
<p><a class="bf515758d605b587210d7f4efe1d63f6a" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/privacy-policy.html" rel="nofollow">Privacy Policy</a></p>
<p><a class="bf515758d605b587210d7f4efe1d63f6a" href="https://taxplanningsanantonio.netlify.app/about-us.html" rel="nofollow">About Us</a></p>
</p>
</div><div class="col-lg-3">
<div>
<p>Follow us</p>
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/InsognaCPAs" class="ffc290b1744bf80889ef4faf595aabec0 facebook" rel="nofollow"><i class="fa fa-facebook"></i></a>
<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/insognacpa-com/" class="pinterest ffc290b1744bf80889ef4faf595aabec0" rel="nofollow"><i class="fa fa-linkedin"></i></a>
<a href="https://www.instagram.com/insognacpa/" class="google ffc290b1744bf80889ef4faf595aabec0-plus" rel="nofollow"><i class="fa fa-instagram"></i></a>
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/@insognacpa7527" class="ffc290b1744bf80889ef4faf595aabec0 youtube" rel="nofollow"><i class="fa fa-youtube"></i></a>
<a href="https://twitter.com/InsognaCPA" class="twitter ffc290b1744bf80889ef4faf595aabec0" rel="nofollow"><i class="fa fa-twitter"></i></a>
</div>
</div></div>
</div>
</footer> 
<script type="text/javascript">
document.addEventListener('DOMContentLoaded', function() {
var dropdowns = document.querySelectorAll('.dropdown-hover');
function showDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'block';
}
function hideDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'none';
}
function handleClick(event) {
var target = event.target;
window.location.href = target.getAttribute('href');
}
dropdowns.forEach(function(dropdown) {
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseenter', showDropdown);
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseleave', hideDropdown);
var dropdownMenu = dropdown.querySelector('.dropdown-toggle');
dropdownMenu.addEventListener('click', handleClick);
});
});
</script> 
</body>
</html>
